Jurassic Park is a movie about trying to keep dinosaurs locked up,
and they escape and kill a bunch of randoms.
(And bad guys!)
Then that happened four more times.
Didn't anyone learn anything...?
Because I sure didn't.
Today, I'M gonna lock up dinosaurs,
but keep the humans alive.
Wait, one already got out?
I haven't even finished the intro yet.
JESUS, this game is morbid!
Now, I can't build my park here... because I'll be reminded of that
poor, faceless blob.
Let's pick the hardest one--- look at this island!
Beautiful, perfect place for people not to die.
Time to create the safest zoo, ever!
Step one: Can't call it Jurassic World.
It's a really bad brand. We'll call it...
"Kilian's Park of Not Dying of Dinosaurs."
That will make the guests feel... secure.
How do we keep that feeling?
In the first movie, Hammond split up the carnivores' and the herbivores' sections.
That park failed.
Let's not do that.
Let's put the giant, nice dinosaurs with the small monsters.
Gonna name the first dinosaur "Grongo".
Because it sounds like a big person name.
Jurassic Park also failed because the raptors were too smart.
We're gonna dumb 'em down from brain cells from Round-Earthers,
and brain cells from people who base their opinions on headlines, but don't read the articles.
(If you feel attacked by that statement, good!)
Damn, those are some expensive dinos.
To make some extra cash, we'll need a restaurant.
Gonna name it "Triceratops Steakhouse", because guess what the beef is made of?
Rats.
And also, a bar.
Because zoos tend to attract horrible children,
and it's the only way to stay sane.
Eventually, we'll build all of these buildings.
...except for the Emergency Shelter,
because that's admitting defeat.
Okay! Let's open the gates.
My dear subscribers...
welcome...
to the thing I said earlier.
(horrific noises from Kilian's mouth which vaguely resemble the Jurassic Park theme)
Everything is going beyond perfect...!
uuuugh. What's that noise?
Grongo, what are you doing?
Grongo? You're supposed to be the NICE dinosaur!
Please don't kill people.
Okay. Close the park.
My -worst- friend raged because his place was too small.
Spoiled brat. We could put twenty college students in a container, and they would THANK us!
Fine, I'll build a new, massive pen, with all kinds of dinos---
big bois, spiky bois, offbrand raptors---
and in the old pen, I'll put, uhh...
well, you see, the game has three different divisions.
Muh Science,
Evil Guy,
and Mall Salesman.
I'm focusing on the entertainment division, because theme parks usually have cute mascots...
but Jurassic Park decided on a seven-tonne mass-murderer.
SEVEN TON MASS MURDERER.
Of course this was gonna be a disaster! The park only had doctors and military people,
and not a single PR guy!
That's why I'm gonna focus on helping him: Because commercials save lives.
Now everything is going beyond SUPER-perfection!
...Except for the small detail that I'm losing $73k a minute.
I'm sure it's not helping that the not-raptors are eating my attractions.
That's another $400,000.
What are these giant meat-eaters, -really?-
Exactly! They are bullies.
Back in school, our counsellor, she would tell us that the best way to stop a bully
was to bribe a bigger bully.
She was a mafia member in Witness Protection.
The biggest carnivore is the Spinosaurus.
The bad guy from
...no-one saw that one.
It's-it's a fish-dinosaur.
I'm gonna put on in every enclosure, as a guard.
Bribe them with goats.
No human has died for five minutes!
All of my dinosaurs died.
Well, except for, of course,
=GRONGOOO=
He stomped the fishie,
then escaped and stomped people.
Can't even protect my performers.
That's the REAL problem in these movies, isn't it?
That they were theme parks.
I'm investing ALL in security,
turning this into a dino-penetentiary.
More helicopters!
Security centres!
We'll turn tranquilizer guns into tranquilizer machineguns!
MORE helicopters! And behind four electric walls...
we'll put...
=GRONGOOOO!=
He'll never escape!
...No guests? How do you pay for all this?
I sell dead dinosaurs to Subway.
Y'know what, Chris Pratt fought two different genetically-enhanced dinos,
I'm so secure in my security, I'm going to put both of them in the same pen.
...Okay. So I have one of them.
Then he left through the front door.
I didn't open that.(yeah right)
Electricity offline? All doors open?!
Sabotage!
At least it's only my employees dying. They can't tell the press, because of contracts.
I still need to know who did this, because I can't sell THESE corpses to Subway.
...I think?
The entertainment division did it! Because of jealousy!
Why did your sabotage need to kill fifty people?
You could have just written a bad review on TripAdvisor!
How should I deal with sabotage?
Maybe allow tranquilizer guns to be used on humans?
No, that's inhumane.
But not inhumane enough.
And, a waste of darts.
If we don't like an employee, let's feed them to the dinosaurs. Who's gonna stop me? Costa Rica?
Sabotage not likely? Too bad!
The carnivores like wet food.
Now, everything is perfect: This isn't a zoo. This isn't even a prison!
This is a fortress! And only an act of GOD could free-
---a tornado.
Walked right into that one.
I can't keep these dinos locked up.
Whatever I do, life, uhh,
finds a path.
I finally understand what Goldblum was saying.
We can't keep these beautiful creatures.(hi godzilla)
They should be free.
To exterminate humanity!
YES, Jeff!
DINOSAURS should rule, and humanity drool!
That's the point of science: To destroy all humans.
We shall mass-produce an army of perfect predators!
Not only on this island, on ALL of the islands---
except, ew, except this one.
Not only predators, weapons! And tanks!
Anyone is allowed into MY army.
Except you-know-who.
Train them like Spartans!
No more grass, only protein.
I think we're ready now. I need them angry.
I'll play "Take on Me" on loud speakers, but remove the chorus.
Yes! Get angry! Escape your cages!
Kill all humans!
Let's return to the first island, to see the chaos of-
what the hell happened?
Five-star rating? Happy tourists?!
Who put all the dinosaurs back in their cages?
Could... could it be? He's not here.
Godspeed, you son of a bitch.
(10 years later spongebob timecard)
That was years ago.
We never found the lad.
But, uh, there's a rumour going around that a Texas Sheriff could be a thirty-foot lizard.
But that could be anyone.
All I know... is that the story isn't over, for...
=GRONGOOOOOO!=
(That seems to have been the Kilean Experience.)
(Really. Nothing left.)
(Sub to the guy?)